这不是"大船  小船  好多船"的妞吗
It's "boats, boats, boats"!
-泰德  快看  -看到了
- Ted, look! - Uh, yeah.
我是说  对  我看过她的广告
I mean, yeah, I know her from that commercial.
大船  小船  好多船
Boats, boats, boats!
也只看过广告而已
And only from that commercial.
才怪  你和她上过床  你忘了吗
No, you banged her. Remember?
还上过好多次呢
Like, a bunch of times.
你上了"大床  小床  好多床"
You knocked "boots, boots, boots."
够了  船长  昨晚到底发生了什么事
All right, captain. What the hell happened here last night?
昨晚  船钟刚刚打了第四次[凌晨两点]
Well, it was just after four bells.
你好
Ahoy!
我知道很晚了
Hi, I-I know it's late,
但我要离开这
But I've got to get out of here.
于是我派了车过去  她到了后
So I sent the car. When she got here...
莉莉  见到你真...
Lily, what a lovely...
我能借用洗手间吗
Can I use your powder room?
然后她去了洗手间
And then she went to the powder room.